eatlime.com 2018-10-28

# EatLime Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.eatlime.com/) : EatLime Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how EatLime uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. 

Eat Lime is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

#### What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you fill out a form on the EatLime website. 

When using our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, location, phone number or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

#### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

• Internal record keeping.  
• We may use the information to improve our products and services. 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

#### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

#### Cookies 

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### EatLime Disclaimer

Please note that EatLime does not offer any guarantees regarding the contractors or service provider that you the user chooses, EatLime does not endorse any particular service, company or contractor. It is the users full responsibility to appraise the contractor, company or service provider prior to entering into a contract with them, and EatLime is not liable for any disputes or claims either the user or contractor or service provider may enter into. 

#### Third party links 

We do not monitor or review the content of other party's websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. EatLime not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.

#### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to the EatLime privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If you have any queries regarding the EatLime policies please contact us.
